[
    {
        "question_id": 1,
        "question_text": "1 day = hours?",
        "question_type": "quiz",
        "options": [
            "a",
            "sa",
            "dd",
            "24"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "4",
        "active": false,
        "times_shown": 23,
        "times_correct": 16
    },
    {
        "question_id": 2,
        "question_text": "what is the first month of english calender?",
        "question_type": "free-form",
        "options": null,
        "correct_answer": "january",
        "active": true,
        "times_shown": 31,
        "times_correct": 21
    },
    {
        "question_id": 3,
        "question_text": "1 hour = minutes?",
        "question_type": "free-form",
        "options": null,
        "correct_answer": "60",
        "active": true,
        "times_shown": 23,
        "times_correct": 11
    },
    {
        "question_id": 4,
        "question_text": "1 month = days?",
        "question_type": "free-form",
        "options": null,
        "correct_answer": "30",
        "active": true,
        "times_shown": 24,
        "times_correct": 9
    },
    {
        "question_id": 5,
        "question_text": "1 year = days?",
        "question_type": "free-form",
        "options": null,
        "correct_answer": "365",
        "active": true,
        "times_shown": 24,
        "times_correct": 13
    },
    {
        "question_id": 6,
        "question_text": "how many letter in 'abc'?",
        "question_type": "quiz",
        "options": [
            "7",
            "3",
            "29",
            "24"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "2",
        "active": true,
        "times_shown": 32,
        "times_correct": 5
    },
    {
        "question_id": 7,
        "question_text": "Primary color?",
        "question_type": "quiz",
        "options": [
            "red",
            "yellow",
            "blue",
            "all"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "4",
        "active": true,
        "times_shown": 10,
        "times_correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question_id": 8,
        "question_text": "where Laura live?",
        "question_type": "quiz",
        "options": [
            "Germany",
            "Belgium",
            "Finland"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "1",
        "active": true,
        "times_shown": 4,
        "times_correct": 4
    },
    {
        "question_id": 9,
        "question_text": "Where you study?",
        "question_type": "quiz",
        "options": [
            "online",
            "physical"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "1",
        "active": false,
        "times_shown": 0,
        "times_correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question_id": 37144,
        "question_text": "Test question",
        "question_type": "quiz",
        "options": [
            "Option 1",
            "Option 2"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "1",
        "active": true,
        "times_shown": 0,
        "times_correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question_id": 18744,
        "question_text": "Test question",
        "question_type": "quiz",
        "options": [
            "Option 1",
            "Option 2"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "1",
        "active": true,
        "times_shown": 0,
        "times_correct": 0
    }
]